handmark.com 2007-08-15

# Handmark - Privacy Notice

Handmark knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Handmark.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

**What Personal Information Does Handmark.com Gather?**

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Handmark.com. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you. 
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Handmark.com. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at Handmark.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist. 

**What About Cookies?**

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as personalized product spotlights and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits. 
  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Handmark.com's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

**Does Handmark.com Share the Information It Receives?**

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below and with subsidiaries Handmark.com, Inc. controls that either are subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice. 

  * **Developer-Partners:** We sell offerings from other developers at Handmark.com. In some cases, we provide information to these developers so they can fulfill and provide support for their products. 
  * **Agents:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 
  * **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Handmark, Inc., or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 
  * **Protection of Handmark and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Handmark, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 
  * We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. 
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**Which Information Can I Access?**

Handmark.com gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with Handmark.com for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. 

**What Choices Do I Have?**

  * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such Handmark.com features. 
  * You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the "Which Information Can I Access?" section above. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. 
  * If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Newsletter Preferences. (If you do not want to receive "Conditions of Use" and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of Handmark.com, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.) 
  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you will not be able to use such important features as personalized settings and saving your shopping cart for later use. 

**Children**

Handmark.com does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use Handmark.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit Handmark.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of New Hampshire. If you have any concern about privacy at Handmark.com, please send us a thorough description to support@Handmark.com, and we will try to resolve it. 

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
